<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Whisky Weekend</title>
    <link>https://webwhiskyweekend.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Web Whisky Weekend</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://webwhiskyweekend.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Whisky</title>
      <link>https://webwhiskyweekend.com/the-whisky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webwhiskyweekend.com/the-whisky/</guid>
      <description>The WhiskyA tremendous selection of fine bourbons, scotches, and other whisky, not to mention some great wine and everything youneed to make delicious cocktails.
You&#39;re guaranteed to find something tasty.Everyone is required to bring at least one bottle of something they enjoy so the selection is always interesting. Mostpeople bring more, and there&#39;s a good assortment provided. We even made an app to keep track of it all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Food</title>
      <link>https://webwhiskyweekend.com/the-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webwhiskyweekend.com/the-food/</guid>
      <description>The FoodYour Web Whisky Weekend ticket includes all the food and drink for the entire weekend (unless we decide to go out for ameal, but who would do that?). All food is prepared fresh on site by people who really know how to cook.
Previous year&#39;s menus have included:Breakfast
Fresh scrambled migas with bell pepper, jalapeño, onion, and chorizoBreakfast omelettes with spinach, sausage or bacon, with white cheddar cheese gritsSteel-cut oatmealFresh fruitLunch/Dinner</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The People</title>
      <link>https://webwhiskyweekend.com/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webwhiskyweekend.com/people/</guid>
      <description>The PeopleGreat people have great conversations. The people at Web Whisky Weekend are both leaders in their fields and really funto talk to.
Attendees IncludeJina5 year alumniDesign Systems Expert. Organizer of Clarity. Previously: Amazon, Salesforce,Apple, Github.
Jonathan Snook5 year alumniDesigner, Developer, Speaker, Author, and Creator of SMACSS. Previously: Xero,Shopify, Yahoo, Squarespace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The House</title>
      <link>https://webwhiskyweekend.com/the-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webwhiskyweekend.com/the-house/</guid>
      <description>The HouseOver 12,000 sq.ft. of luxury including a pool, hot tub, separate pool house, large fire pit, full size volleyball court,tether ball, corn hole boards, croquet, small basketball court, some frisbee golf targets (bring your own discs) and a16 seat home theater.
The Ark on Lake LanierAccommodates 45 People with 14 sleeping areas, including 8 king, 3 queen, 1 full and 15 twin beds, the Ark has room for 10 different families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Register Now</title>
      <link>https://webwhiskyweekend.com/register/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://webwhiskyweekend.com/register/</guid>
      <description>Registration Opens Feb 15, 2020Important Pricing Info:All private bedrooms and full-size beds in shared rooms include attendance for two people. You can book them for yourself or bring a +1, up to you.Kathy&#39;s Cabin includes the entire cabin (which can technically sleep 3 people).Lots of rooms to choose from.
 Download the Bedroom Guide</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>